Inventory of the Oleg Nikolaevich Moskvin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Newspapers, 1988-1999
  - Pravda, 1988 October 1-1989 December 10 (Folder 11: 9)
  - Proletariĭ, no. 1(8) and 5(5), 1995-1996 (Folder 12: 4)
  - Rabochaia demokratiia, nos. 13 and 14/15, 1993 (Folder 12: 4)
  - Rabochee deistvie, no. 1, 1992 (Folder 12: 4)
  - Rabochiĭ antifashist, no. 1(1), 1996 (Folder 12: 5)
  - Sankt-Peterburgskie vedomosti, 1991 October 19 (Folder 11: 10)
  - Serp i molot, no. 10(31), 1995 (Folder 11: 10)
  - Smena, 1989 March 3-1992 February 15 (Folder 11: 10)
  - Soobshchaet IRA, no. 9(13), 1992 (Folder 12: 5)
  - Studencheskaia zashchita, nos. 9 and 12, 1995 (Folder 10: 28)
  - Tribuna oppozitsii, no. 3, 1994 (Folder 12: 5)
  - Trud, 1993 November 6 (Folder 11: 11)
  - Veche, 1993 (Folder 12: 6)
  - Vecherniĭ Leningrad, 1989 August 21-1990 April 24 (Folder 11: 11)
  - Vecherniĭ Peterburg, 1992 May 12 and June 30 (Folder 11: 11)
  - Za rabochee delo, nos. 8(23), 9(24) and undated, 1994 (Folder 12: 6)
  - Zavtra, nos. 40, 49, 50, 1998-1999 (Folder 11: 12)